Respectfully addressed to:

Human Resource Department **Robert Bosch Vietnam Co. Ltd** Unit 11.7, e-town 2, Cong Hoa street, Ho Chi Minh City

Dear Sir/Madam,

I am pleased to express to you herewith my interest and enthusiasm for the post of Architect (Software Development) in Robert Bosch Vietnam Company Limited.

I am a software engineer with 6 years of experience working for software, service and manufacturing companies, especially nearly 2 years as an in-house software development team leader and a SAP ERP project team member in a manufacturing company.

I have experience in designing new software as well as restructuring existing software. I also have good practice in maintenance of legacy software system. This process helps me to know what the good software architecture should be, not only for running in present but also for retaining in the future.

Moreover, with the diploma of Master of Computer Science certified by Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology (HCMC BK), I am confident of having a solid technical background as well as efficient methods to approach new domains and to solve problems.

For those reasons, I am confident that my experience and skills are suitable for the job of Software Development Architect. And most of all, I like the manufacturing industry.

I would like to emphasize again my expectation to work for Robert Bosch. I believe that a great brand name like Robert Bosch is a professional working environment for creative and eager-for-learning employees, where I will be able to contribute my best to the organization's success in a long term co-operation.

Please refer to my attached CV for more detailed information.

I can be reached via my cell phone, 0918 923 613, or through email, leanhhuy3681@gmail.com / leanhhuy3681@yahoo.com.

I look forward to an interview on this employment opportunity.

Thanks for your time and consideration.

Faithfully yours,

Huy, Le Anh

RESUME OF LE ANH HUY

LE ANH HUY

IT Assistant Manager

Mobile: 0918 923 613

Email: leanhhuy3681@gmail.com, leanhhuy3681@yahoo.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Become an IT manager in the next 5 years

EDUCATION

Time	University	Diploma
2007 - 2010	Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology	Master of Computer Science
2005	Ho Chi Minh City University of Education	Certificate of Educational Psychology
2000 - 2005	Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology	Bachelor of Computer Science &
		Engineering

^{*} Expertise: Software Development, ERP, MIS

WORKING EXPERIENCE

GREAT EASTERN LIFE VIETNAM (a Singaporean life insurance company)

Assistant Manager (June 2011 - Present)

- Working as an in-house senior software engineer, coordinating with Business Analyst team to analyze, develop and maintain management specific applications for life insurance industry
- Coordinating with regional IT team to fix defects in corporation level
- Managing configurations of production, UAT and SIT servers of localized applications
- Being the main in charge of the Insurance Policy Quotation Printing solution
- Technologies: Java/JSP, Oracle
- Report to: IT Director

SOFTELIANCE (a French software company)

Senior Software Developer (May 2010 - May 2011)

- Projects are business/management applications: Cash-back website, Heating & Watering Service Management, Head Hunting website, Invoicing, Customer Care, DVD Rental Station...
- Most are distributed solutions with central local databases.
- Customers are small and mid-size companies in Europe (mostly in France and Be-Ne-Lux) of various industries: Human Resource, Purchasing Service, Finance & Accounting, e-Commerce...
- Technologies: C#, ASP.NET, WinForm, SQL Server 2005/2008, JQuery
- Report to: French Project Manager

THIEN LONG GROUP (a Vietnamese stationery manufacturing & trading company)

SAP ERP Project Team Member (August 2008 - February 2009)

- Playing the role of key IT person for Material Management module, backup person for Production Planning module
- Working as the bridge engineer between foreign SAP consultants and end users, identifying risks/problems (especially conflicts and misunderstandings) and taking proper actions to prevent/solve
- Handling technologies and business processes transferred from consulting partners to support the SAP ERP system after go-live

- Working as a business analyst to help end users in requirement & data analyzing, business process standardizing, translating/interpreting...
- Report to: ERP Project Director
- Project size: 50 people from 4 different companies (2 foreign and 2 domestic)

Software Team Leader (May 2007 - July 2008)

- Managing the programming team of 3 people to develop in-house management applications
- Being the main IT person in charge of all management applications: Accounting (EFFECT), Electronic Custom Portal (ECUS), Sale & Inventory, Assembly Management, Goods Issue & Invoice Printing, ISO Document Management, Leave Management, Time Sheet Calculation, Shareholder Management...
- Being the administrator of all Web, Application & Database servers
- Being the DBA of all databases in SQL Server 2000/2005 (backup, security & turning)
- Coordinating with the System/Network administrator in maintaining the whole IT system
- Taking part in ERP project preparation: evaluating solutions, conducting As-Is interviews, collecting requirements, recruiting IT team members...
- <u>Technologies:</u> C#/VB.NET, WinForm, ASP.NET, Crystal Report, SQL Server 2000/2005, Windows Server 2000/2003
- Significant contributions:
 - + Go-live the Sale & Inventory application
 - + Make documents for applications, databases and servers
 - + Propose and implement feasible security & backup solutions
 - + Identify potential risks in the legacy IT system
- Report to: IT Director

APEX VIETNAM TOURIST (a Japanese tourism company)

Software Developer (September 2005 - April 2007)

- Working as a software developer of Tri Nhan software company, a subsidiary of APEX
- Coding, testing, deploying & maintaining application software; collecting and analyzing customer requirements; analyzing and designing database
- Supporting manager in architect designing and project scheduling
- Projects: Hotel Reservation website, Stock Exchange website, Technical Analyst application, Company portal, Charting application...
- Technologies: C#, ASP.NET, WinForm, SQL Server 2000/2005, PostgreSql
- Report to: Project Manager

LANGUAGES

- Vietnamese: mother tongue
- English: TOEFL ITP 533 (certified in March 2011), with additional experience in interpreting and translating business content.

SOFT SKILLS

- **Communication**: Good at communicating with both technical staff and business people; able to collect information from domain experts (from staff to manager)
- **Analysis**: Good at both technical and business analysis

STRONG POINTS

- **Flexibility:** able to work from various environments as well as different positions (software engineer, business analyst, project coordinator)
- **Effective approach**: can learn new industries and technologies quickly
- **Critical thinking**: view problems in various aspects to find out the most efficient solution; apply 80/20 Principle, Mistake Proofing, 7 Tools... whenever possible

KNOWLEDGE

- Comprehensive understanding of an ERP project, especially SAP ERP
- General knowledge of business processes of a company, especially a manufacturing company
- Basic knowledge of life insurance

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- <u>Software design:</u> OOP & Design patterns, Enterprise Application Architect patterns, Framework design & implementation, N-tier design, Database design
- <u>Software development:</u> analysis, design, development, testing, deployment and maintenance
- Programming language & technique: C#, VB.NET, ASP.NET, Java/JSP, Web service, AJAX, Web font-end (HTML, CSS, JavaScript/JQuery), SQL, C++/MFC, ABAP (basic), XML, UML, O/R mapping, Code generation
- <u>Tool:</u> VS.NET (2003, 2005, 2008, 2010), Eclipse, NetBeans, Crystal Report (basic), CaliberRM,
 VS 6.0
- Version management: Visual SourceSafe, Subversion
- DBA: SQL Server (intermediate level)
- DBMS: SQL Server (2000, 2005, 2008), Oracle (basic), MySQL (basic), PostgreSQL, FireBird
- <u>Server:</u> IIS, Tomcat, Windows Server 2000/2003
- Good practices in legacy system handling, data conversion, software restructuring and database refactoring

AVAILABILITY

A 30-calendar-day notice in advance is needed.

REMUNERATION

The expected salary is open for negotiation.

REFERENCES

Reference contacts are available upon request.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full name: Lê Anh Huy DOB: June 3th, 1981

Nationality: Vietnamese <u>Identity number:</u> 273 605 480

Gender: Male Religion: None

Mobile phone: 0918 923 613 Skype: leanhhuy3681

Email: leanhhuy3681@gmail.com, leanhhuy3681@yahoo.com

Mailing address: 159/39 Pham Van Hai Street, Ward 5, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City, Viet Nam

HUY, LE ANH

Last update: February 15th, 2012